[MUSIC PLAYING]
嗨，大家好，罗伯
Welcome back to the show.
欢迎回到我们的计划
So I got on Twitter recently and I
您最近进入Twitter
asked folks, what would they like to see
我问人们他们想要什么
in upcoming Polycasts.
在即将播出的Polycasts剧集中观看吗？
And kind of resoundingly, a lot of folks
决定了
said they want to see more Firebase.
他们想从Firebase看更多。
So I thought it would be cool to kind of kick off
所以我认为那会很酷
a multi-part series where we talk
如果我们从一个多部分的系列开始，我们谈论
about how you can integrate Polymer and Firebase together
如何将Polymer和Firebase合并在一起
into your projects.
在您的项目中。
So today, what we're going to do is just get started.
所以我们今天要做的只是开始
We're going to set up a very simple Firebase project
设置Firebase项目非常简单
and we're going to do some Firebase authentication.
我们将进行一些Firebase验证
So follow me over here to my laptop.
所以在我的笔记本电脑上跟随我
And the first thing I'm going to do
我要做的第一件事是
is I'm going to go to console.firebase.google.com.
转到console.firebase.google.com。
You'll want to have a Google account
您需要一个个人Google帐户
already that you can sign into.
您可以通过它登录。
So I've signed into my personal account here.
所以我登录了我的个人帐户
And I'm going to create a new project for my Firebase app.
我将为Firebase应用程序创建一个新项目。
And this is going to let me do all sorts of really
这将使我有资格做很多事情
cool things.
奇妙的事情。
I can do hosting with Firebase, I
我可以托管Firebase
can do database work with Firebase, authentication, et
创建Firebase数据库，进行身份验证，
cetera.
Etcetera。
I got to give it a name.
我得给她起个名字
So I'm going to call this poly-fire,
所以我选择了“ poly-fire”
or something like that.
或类似的东西。
And we'll create that project.
我们将建立这个项目。
Firebase will go off.
Firebase将启动。
It'll think for a second.
他会思考一秒钟。
The hamster wheels are spinning up.
出现动画圈
poly-fire is getting created and released into the world.
多重射击完成并释放。
OK.
好吧，太好了。
After that's done, you're going to see a dashboard that
完成该阶段后，将出现一个仪表板
looks kind of like this.
看起来像这样。
And there's a bunch of options and things right here.
这里有几个选项和东西。
It can be a little bit overwhelming.
可能很多。
But we're going to start off really, really small,
但是我们将开始非常简单的开始
and the only thing that we're going to really deal with today
我们今天要解决的唯一一件事
is authentication.
是身份验证。
And so what I want to do is click on this authentication
我需要做的就是单击一个选项卡
tab, and it's going to ask me, up here at the top,
这种身份验证，我将在顶部看到选择
what sort of sign in methods I would
适用于任何类型的登录方式
like to allow in this app.
我将为此应用程序允许它。
Now being a Googler, I got to represent.
现在我在Google工作，我必须代表它。
So I'm going to enable Google sign in.
因此，我将激活Google登录。
And we just flip this little switch and click Save.
我们按下执行按钮并保存。
And what this is going to let us do,
这将给我们带来的是
is anybody who's got a Google account will
拥有Google帐户的任何人都可以拥有它
be able to hit a sign in button and sign
按登录按钮
in through that account in our Firebase app.
并使用该帐户登录Firebase。
The other thing that we need to do,
我们需要做的另一件事
is we need to go over here to our settings,
进入设置
go to Project Settings, and we're
然后项目设置
going to need this web API key that I'm copying here.
我们需要在此处复制的Web API密钥。
Otherwise our authentication will not work.
否则，我们的身份验证将不起作用。
So copy that.
所以复制。
OK.
知道了
So I think that's basically everything we
我认为这就是我们所需要的
need in the Firebase console.
主要在Firebase控制台中。
There's a ton more that you can do here.
还有更多事情要做。
with just the default setup.
默认情况下。
So the next thing I want to do is switch over
所以下一步
to my command line.
要转到我的命令行。
And I've already gone ahead and created a directory
您已经创建了一个目录
to hold my demo application.
要安装我的演示应用程序。
And Firebase also provides a really useful set
Firebase还提供了有用的集合
of command line tools that you can install that will go ahead
从可以安装的命令行工具
and scaffold a project for you.
为您制作一个项目。
So if you don't have those installed already,
因此，如果您尚未安装它们
you can do npm install -g firebase-tools.
您可以执行npm install-g firebase-tools。
That'll go out, fetch all that stuff, set it up for you,
他会去带所有这些东西，为你做准备，
so you'll now have a Firebase command.
因此，您将拥有一个Firebase命令。
I've already got those installed so you don't have
您已经安装了它们
to watch me do any of that.
我不需要看着我这样做。
So what I'm going to do, is I'm going to run firebase init.
因此，我要做的是运行Firebase自述文件。
And it's going to put a very rad emoji on my screen.
屏幕上会出现一个很棒的表情符号。
And then it's going to ask me some questions about what
然后一群人会问我有关
sort of Firebase features I would
什么样的Firebase属性
like to have in this project.
我想参加我的项目。
Firebase provides a real time database, which is awesome,
Firebase提供了一个瞬时数据库，这很棒
and we will be using that, so we'll leave that checked.
我们将使用它，因此将其打勾。
And then we've got Firebase hosting.
然后我们得到了Firebase托管。
And that lets us basically just do hosting of static assets.
这基本上使我们有资格仅托管固定资产。
We can host our entire site on Firebase if we want.
如果需要，我们可以将整个站点托管在Firebase上。
So I will leave that in there as well.
所以我也将其留在那里。
I'll hit enter.
然后按回车。
It's going to ask us what project
任何项目都会问我们
we want to associate with.
我们想加入他。
So since we just created that one called poly-fire.
因此，自从我们创建了一个名为poly-fire的项目以来。
Here I'll move this up a little bit,
我将其上移一点
this is a little easier to see.
使我更容易看到。
So we will associate with poly-fire.
因此，我们将加入poly-fire。
What file should be associated with the database?
我们应将哪个文件加入数据库？
We'll just use the default value there database.rules.json.
我们将仅在database.rules.json中使用默认值。
What directory do you want to use?
您要使用哪个指南？
We'll say our public one.
我们将选择公共目录。
And then it's going to ask if Firebase should
然后他会问他是否应该在Firebase上
sort of configure its local server
一种配置其本地服务器规则
rules to direct everything to index.html?
要将所有内容都指向index.html？
So if we were building a single page web app.
因此，如果我们要构建一个一页的Web应用程序
because that's pretty cool.
因为那太好了。
And at that point, it's basically done.
我们可以说到此为止我们已经完成了。
And if we go ahead and we open this up in our code editor,
如果我们在代码编辑器中打开它
we'll see that this has started to kind of scaffold
我们将看到它开始创建
some things out for us.
对我们来说有些事情。
So I've got these firebase.json, firebaserc file
所以我有一个firebase.json和一个firebaserc文件
that points to my project name, stuff like that.
它指的是我的项目的名称，诸如此类。
This is all just configuration to make Firebase work.
所有这些都将初始化，直到Firebase正常工作为止。
What we're mainly going to be working with today
我们今天基本上要做的是
though is this public directory.
虽然，这是一个公共指南
So this is where our code is going to live.
这就是我们的代码所在的位置。
The other nice thing that we can do with the Firebase tools,
我们可以使用Firebase工具做的另一件事
is we can start up a local dev server.
是从本地开发服务器开始的。
So we'll say firebase serve.
因此，我们将编写Firebase服务。
And it's actually going to look at the rules
他将考虑规则
that we have in our firebase.json there.
我们在firebase.json中拥有。
That tells it to serve our public directory.
告诉他充当我们公共目录的服务器。
So we can then just open up localhost:5000.
我们可以打开localhost：5000
And you'll see a page that looks like this.
您会看到一个这样的页面。
Letting you know that your local instance of Firebase
告诉您您的Firebase本地模型
is working.
作品。
Cool.
太好了
All right.
知道了
The next thing we want to do, is we
我们需要做的下一个命令
want to go ahead and install Polymer,
是我们安装聚合物吗
and we want to install Polymer Fire.
我们要安装Polymer Fire。
Which is a set of Polymer elements
它是聚合物元素的集合
that work specifically with Firebase.
专门用于Firebase。
So, because I want everything to live in this public directory,
所以因为我希望所有内容都在公共目录中
I'm actually going to create a bowerrc file.
我将创建一个bowerrc文件。
So I'll create a .bowerrc file.
因此，我将创建一个.bowerrc文件。
So .bowerrc.
所以.bowerrc。
RC And I will use this to tell bower
RC，我将用它来告诉凉亭
to install all my stuff into that public dir.
将我所有的工具安装在公共目录中。
So I will say, directory is public/bower_components.
所以我写的目录是public / bower_components。
Cool.
太好了
And then in my terminal, bower init.
然后在我的工作站上，启动凉亭。
Yeah, it'll ask us a bunch of questions about our project,
会问我们一些有关我们项目的问题
we can just use the default values, that's fine.
我们可以使用默认值，这没有问题。
And then we will bower install --save.
然后，我们将安装bower-保存。
We will definitely want Polymer/polymer.
毫无疑问，我们将需要聚合物/聚合物。
We're going to want firebase/polymerfire.
我们将需要一个火力基地/ Polymerfire。
All right, so that's going to go out and fetch
好吧，这工作的方法是
all of those resources and dump them into our public directory.
将所有这些资源放入公共目录中。
And now we're basically ready to start building our app.
现在我们准备创建自己的应用程序。
And remember the goal of this app
并记住此应用程序的目标
is to basically have sort of a simple sign in flow
基本上就是用户得到
So all I'm going to build today is a button, that when
所以我今天要做的就是创建一个按钮
you click on it, it'll take you through the o-auth flow
当您单击它时，它将使您顺利进行o-auth
for Google sign in.
使用Google登录。
And when the user is actually signed in,
用户已经登录时
it'll just like display their name on screen.
他的名字将出现在屏幕上。
That way we know we at least have something working there.
这样我们就知道系统可以正常工作。
So, let's go into our index.html file.
所以我们去index.html
And there's a bunch of code here that Firebase sort of set up
Firebase编写的一组代码
because I don't really need any of this stuff.
因为我不需要它们。
We'll get rid everything in the body.
我们将摆脱这个小组的一切
And make this a little bit bigger.
我将其做大一点。
We'll rename this Firebase Auth or something like that.
我们将重命名此Firebase身份验证。
And because we're using Polymer, because we're
而且因为我们使用聚合物，并且因为我们
by creating just a my app element, that can sort of hold
创建应用程序元素，您可以
all of my logic.
容纳我的整个系统。
So I'll have a my-app element here.
所以我要把我的应用放在这里。
And I'm going to make sure to include an HTML
我会确保包括
import for that.
为此导入HTML。
So we're going to ask for my-app.html.
因此，我将询问my-app.html。
OK.
知道了
And inside of this my-app element, my-app.html,
在此my-app元素my-app.html中
we're going to want to import some of the Polymer Fire
我们将需要导入一些元素
elements.
聚合物火。
So let's go check those out really quick.
因此，让我们快速检查一下。
So we'll going to beta.webcomponents.org.
因此，我们将转到beta.webcomponents.org。
This is the new catalog where you
这是新目录
can find all sorts of interesting, custom elements.
我们可以找到各种定制物品。
The ones that I'm looking for are called polymerfire.
我正在寻找的一种叫做Polymerfire。
So go check these out.
所以我会检查一下。
So this is a suite of elements created by the Firebase team
这是Firebase团队创建的元素的集合
specifically for Polymer.
专门用于聚合物。
And you can see here that basically what we want
您可以在这里看到我们基本需要的
is this firebase-app element, and we're
这是firebase-app元素
going to combine it with this firebase-auth element.
我们将其与firebase-auth元素结合在一起。
So when I bower installed these, I got both of these already.
所以当我使用群组管理器安装它们时，我已经安装了它们
But you can sort of see the signature for how these work.
但是您会看到一个信号，说明它们如何工作
Here, I'll bump this up a little bit so you can read that.
我将其放大一些，以便您阅读。
So you create a firebase-app element.
因此，您正在创建一个Firebase应用程序
you give it that API key that we copied earlier,
您提供了我们先前复制的API密钥
and you create a firebase-auth element,
并创建一个firebase-auth元素。
and that'll tell you when your user is signed in or not.
并告诉他们用户何时登录。
Right.
知道了
So far so good.
到目前为止非常好。
So in our my-app element, over here.
所以在我们的元素my-app中
I basically want to create an element that's
我想创建一个物品
going to hold that firebase-app element.
容纳firebase-app元素。
So I've got some code here that I've already written.
因此，这里有一个我已经编写的代码。
Kind of stolen from another project.
从另一个项目中偷来的。
And let's go through and we'll update this a little bit,
让我们回顾一下，我会对其进行一些更新
I can explain what's happening.
我可以解释发生了什么。
So I've got a dom-module from my-app element.
所以我有一个来自我的应用程序的dom模块。
I got this firebase-app element inside of here.
我从这里得到了一个firebase-app元素。
And I want to give it the domain for my project.
我想给他我的项目ID。
So if we go back to Firebase, we go back to the console,
因此，如果我们回到Firebase，我们将返回控制面板
we look at our project settings, what it actually wants
看看我们的项目设置，您真正想要的是什么
is this Project ID right here.
这个项目在这里被标记。
So it says Polymer fire, or poly-fire-11d42.
因此，如前所述，Polymer fire或poly-fire-11d42。
So that's what we're going to use.
这就是我们要使用的。
So our auth-domain is going to be poly-fire-11d42.
因此，我们的auth域将是poly-fire-11d42。
Our database URL, even though we're not using it yet,
数据库的URL，即使我们不使用它
we can go ahead and set that up.
我们可以准备。
And then our API key is going to be that one that we copied.
然后将复制API密钥。
So get rid of that and we'll drop in the API key
因此，我们将摆脱它，并用API密钥替换它
that we copied there.
我们复制到那里。
And the last thing I'm going to do,
我要做的最后一件事。
is I'm going to have this log in element
我将获得登录项
that I'm going to create.
我将要创建的。
But essentially this is all that my app is going to do for us.
但基本上这就是我的应用程序所要做的。
It's going to set up the connection to Firebase app,
将建立一个到Firebase的链接
and then it's going to have a little log in element that
然后将获得一个登录项
will sort of toggle on and off.
它将在进入和退出之间切换。
Let's go ahead and create that.
我们去创建它。
Create a my-login.html.
创建my-login.html。
So again, I've got a little bit of code
再说一遍，我有代码
that I'm going to steal and drop in here just
我会偷去放到这里
to start to scaffold out my log in element.
只是开始创建一个登录项。
What I want to do, is I want to make sure
我要做的就是确保
that I am importing the Firebase app elements.
导入Firebase应用项目。
I'm going to steal this link tag here.
我将在这里窃取此链接卡。
I don't have it in any of my snippets
在我的任何惩罚中都不存在
now that I'm using Visual Studio Code.
现在我正在使用Visual Studio Code
It's making me like the world's slowest developer.
这使我成为世界上最慢的开发人员。
So if anybody wants to create a Visual Studio Code snippets
因此，如果有人想创建一个代码段包
package for Polymer.
用于聚合物的Visual Studio代码
I would totally be your best friend.
我会成为你最好的朋友。
What we're going to do is we're going to import
我将导入
bower_components/, is it polymerfire I believe.
bower_components /，我认为是Polymerfire
polymerfire/firebase-auth.
polymerfire / firebase-auth。
All right.
好吧
So polymerfire/firebase-auth.html.
因此，polymerfire / firebase-auth.html。
And we're also going to pull in the paper button.
我们还将拖动纸张按钮。
We'll have paper-button/paper-button.html.
我们将有paper-button / paper-button.html。
It's looking good.
看起来不错
Inside of our template I'm going to drop
我将放入我们的模具中
in a firebase-auth element.
Firebase-auth元素。
This is the basic signature for a firebase-auth element.
这是firebase-auth的基本参考
I want to give it an ID because I
我想给她身份证
am going to need to reference it in JavaScript a little bit.
因为我需要在JavaScript中稍微提一下。
And then it's got a user property
然后您获得一个用户属性
that we are going to expose to the outside world using
我们将向外界展示的
this binding.
使用此绑定。
So we're just going to have a thing called user.
因此，我们将拥有一个称为用户的东西。
It's also got this value called status-known
它还具有名为status-known的值
which could be interesting.
那可能很有趣
It's a boolean that tells you whether or not
布尔值告诉您是否
you can assert the presence of a user, and whether
您可以确认用户是否在场
or not you're allowed to check the user object.
以及是否允许您检查用户对象。
So I'm including it here.
所以我在这里保证。
I'm actually not going to use it in my code today
我今天不会在代码中使用它
because, I'll be 100% honest, I'm not entirely sure
因为，说实话，我不确定
if I need to use it in my code.
如果您需要在代码中使用。
But I am including i there just so you know about it.
但是我保证在那里，以便您知道。
Maybe in the next episode we'll discover
也许在下一集中我们会发现
if it's actually useful or not.
是否有用。
But I'm just going to drop it in there
但是我就留在那里
so it's on everyone's radar.
所以请记住。
And lastly we have this provider value.
最后，我们具有提供者的价值。
Which I'm just going to set to Google.
我将为Google设置。
Because if you remember, we went through,
因为如果您还记得，我们经历了
and when we were in our dashboard,
当我们进入控制面板时
we set up the authentication method as, sign in with Google.
我们已将身份验证方法设置为Google登录名。
The next thing we need to do, is we need
我们需要采取的下一步
to drop in some paper buttons.
正在放一些纸纽扣。
Here all close the side bar so you can see this a bit easier.
我将关闭整个侧边栏，直到您看到更好的为止。
So you have a paper button here, it's raised,
所以我们这里有一个纸按钮
so it'll have a bit of a drop shadow.
因此它的阴影会略低。
And when the user taps it, it's going to run a log in method,
当用户单击它时，他们将打开登录方法
and I've got this little thing that I'm
我这里有事要做
doing here where I'm hiding the button if there is a user
如果有用户，则隐藏按钮
present.
存在。
So if the user is already signed in,
因此，如果用户已经登录
let's not show the sign in button, right?
我们不显示登录按钮，好吗？
And I've got basically the exact same thing going down here
完全一样的事情发生了
for this other button.
对于另一个按钮。
This will be our log out button.
这将是注销按钮。
And we just sort of flip the logic.
我们有点反映了系统。
So if there is already a user, then
因此，如果用户已经存在，则
let's display the log out button.
让我们显示“注销”按钮。
And if there is not a user, we'll
如果没有用户
display the log in button.
我们将显示登录按钮。
Right.
好吧
Cool, so far so good.
太好了，到目前为止一切都很好。
Let's also add a little bit of script
让我们在这里添加文字
here to define our element.
让我们知道我们的元素。
So I will say this element is a my-login element.
因此，我将说此元素对于登录至关重要。
And for the properties, we basically
至于特征，我们基本上
will want to expose this user property.
我们将需要显示此用户属性。
So it's a user.
所以他是用户。
Which is an object.
它是一个对象。
We also want to have that status known property.
我们还需要具有一个已知的status属性。
So status known.
这样一个已知的情况。
And that is also going to be an object.
那也将是一个对象。
OK.
知道了
And now I want to implement these log in and log out
现在我要实现登录方法
methods.
快出去
So these should be pretty straightforward.
因此，它们应该非常清楚。
We're basically just going to use some of the APIs
我们基本上将使用一些API
that the Firebase Auth element expose's for us.
由Firebase身份验证元素显示
So I'm going to just go ahead and paste some code in here
所以我会在这里粘贴一些代码
that I already copied.
我以前复制过的。
And what we're going to do, is we're
而我们要做的是
going to use the ID of the auth element.
使用身份验证元素身份证。
So remember, when we say this .$,
所以请记住，当我们这样说时。
that's Polymer's way of saying reference this thing with this
这是Polymer授权此推荐的方法
ID.
凭此身份证。
So we'll say this .$.auth, sign in with pop up.
因此，我们将说$。Auth，使用弹出窗口登录。
And that method basically tells the auth element
该模式基本上可以教授身份验证元素
to open the o-auth screen and ask someone
它会打开o-auth屏幕，并询问用户
to sign in using Google.
使用Google登录。
For the log out method, it's basically just call sign
对于注销模式，基本需要
out using that.
使用它注销。
The last thing that I want to do,
我想做的最后一件事
is I want to add just a little template here
我想在这里添加模板
that will toggle on and off when we have a user or not.
无论是否存在用户，它都会切换。
And it will display that user's name.
将显示该用户的名称。
Just so we can verify that the user object we get back
这样我们就可以验证用户对象
is correct.
谁恢复正常。
So I've got some code that I'm just going to paste in here.
所以我在这里有粘贴的代码。
And yeah, so I'm using a dom-if.
因此，请使用dom-if。
I'm checking if we have a user already.
我确定我们是否已有用户。
And then I've just got an h1.
然后我得到了h1。
Where I'm just going to bind to the user's display name.
我将其与用户的显示名称相关联。
All right.
好吧
So I think we're pretty close to having everything
所以我认为我们快完成了
where we want it.
在所有步骤中。
Let's just double check all of our imports here.
只要确保所有进口都在这里
We don't want to have a white screen of death.
我们不需要白屏（系统已停止工作）
That does happen from time to time.
它不时发生。
So everything in my-login looks good.
所以关于我的登录的一切看起来都很不错
In my-app we need to make sure that we are importing my-login.
我们需要确保我的应用程序导入了我的登录信息。
So let's do that.
因此，让我们这样做。
Go back up here.
让我们回到这里。
So we will pull in my-login.html.
如果我们拔出my-login.html。
We are also going to want to pull
我们还需要退出
in that firebase-app element.
Firebase应用程序组件。
So polymerfire.
所以聚合物火。
Firebase-app.
Firebase应用程序。
All right.
知道了
And then in our index file, we are
然后在索引文件中
pulling in the my-app element.
然后我们提取一个应用元素。
So my-app contains firebase-app and log in.
所以我的应用程序有一个firebase-app和一个登录名。
And then log in contains firebase-auth.
然后，登录名包含firebase-auth。
Let's cross our fingers and see if this works on the first try.
希望它能在第一时间生效。
We will run the provided Firebase server.
我们将运行锁定的Firebase服务器。
I know sometimes we use Polymer CLI to serve things.
我知道我们有时会使用Polymer CLI来完成这项工作。
But right now I'm just doing everything with the provided
但是我目前使用所有小部件
Firebase tools.
被Firebase锁定
In a later episode, I'll actually
在另一集中，我会告诉你
show how to integrate both Polymer tools and Firebase
如何合并两个聚合物工具
tools.
和Firebase工具。
But for now let's just use the Firebase server.
但是目前我们使用Firebase Server。
And it will tell us that the app is that localhost:5000.
它会告诉我们该应用程序是如此localhost：5000。
So copy that.
因此，我们将其复制。
Drop that in here to the Chrome's.
我们将其放在Chrome浏览器中。
I see I have a sign in button there.
我看到按钮上有一个勾号。
Let's zoom in a little bit so you can see that.
让我们放大一点，以便您看到。
Clicking on that should give me an o-auth pop up.
单击它应该弹出o-auth。
And ask me to sign in.
并请我登录。
And I sign in.
并登录。
And then boom, it says, welcome Rob Dodson.
所以告诉我，你好罗伯·道森（Rob Dodson）。
Lets me know that we have a user object.
告诉我，我们有一个用户对象。
And if I want, I can then sign out.
如果我愿意，我会出去。
And start the process all over again.
我从头开始重新开始这个过程。
So that about covers it for today.
这样就涵盖了今天的一切。
We've now got kind of the basics of setting up
现在，我们涵盖了设置的基础知识
Firebase and setting up Firebase authentication in our project.
Firebase并为我们的项目设置Firebase身份验证。
There's still a lot more to talk about,
还有很多话要说
but I'm going to save that for the next episode.
但是我会在下一集中保留它。
So if you have any questions, as always,
所以，如果您有任何疑问，像往常一样
you can leave them for me down below in the comments.
您可以在下面的评论中留下它们。
Or you can hit me up on a social network of your choosing
或者您可以通过您选择的任何社交网络与我联系
at #askpolymer.
在#askpolymer上。
As always, thanks so much for watching,
和往常一样，感谢您的继续
and I'll see you next time.
下次见。
Hey there, Polycasters, what's up?
嗨，Polycasters，你好吗？
If you liked this episode and you want to see some more,
如果您喜欢那集并且想看更多
you can check them out over here.
您可以在这里检查。
And also be sure to click that little subscribe button,
确保按下共享按钮。
thanks.
谢谢